form-assistance.com 2016-10-17

# Form-Assistance.com

Form-Assistance.com is committed to responsible privacy practices and to complying with United States Law. Our respect for our customers' privacy is paramount. We have policies and procedures to ensure that all personal information is handled in accordance with United States Law. This Privacy Policy sets out our policies on the management of personal information - that is, how we collect personal information, the purposes for which we use this information, and to whom this information is disclosed.

**What is personal information?**

Personal information is information that could identify you. Examples of personal information include your:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Telephone Number
  * Email Address

**How do we collect and use your personal information?**

Any information we collect from you may be used to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * For our Internal Records for account and billing inquiry.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * To improve the quality of service so we can effectively respond to customer service requests and support needs

If you consent, we may also use your information in order For promotional emails about our new products and special offers that can be sent via email.

We may also collect personal information from you through transactions you have with us directly, such as through our contact centres, or online through our website. Where we do this, we will endeavour to inform you why we are collecting your personal information, how we use that information and to whom we intend to disclose it.

**What happens if you don't provide personal information?**

Generally, you have no obligation to provide any personal information requested by us. However, if you choose to withhold requested personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the products and services that depend on the collection of that information. As an example, if you did not provide the personal information, we would be unable to notify you directly of the services that may be applicable to you.

**To whom do we disclose personal information?**

We do not sell, trade or transfer to outside parties your personal identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe that this is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect rights and safety. However, none of your personal information will be provided to other parties for the purpose of marketing, advertising and promotion. 

**How do we protect personal information?**

At all times, we take great care to ensure your personal information is protected from unauthorized access, use, disclosure or alteration.

We endeavour to ensure that our employees are aware of, and comply with, their obligations in relation to the handling of personal information. Only properly authorized employees are permitted to see or use personal information held by Form-Assistance.com and, even then, only to the extent that it is relevant to their roles and responsibilities.

Your personal information will not be sold to any other organization for that organization's unrelated independent use. Further, we will not share your personal information with any organizations, other than those engaged by us to assist us in the provision of our products and services (as described above).

**Is the personal information we hold accurate?**

We endeavour to maintain your personal information as accurately as reasonably possible. However, we rely on the accuracy of personal information as provided to us both directly and indirectly. We encourage you to contact us if the personal information we hold about you is incorrect or to notify us of a change in your personal information. Our contact details are set out below.

**How can you access or correct the personal information we hold about you?**

Wherever possible and appropriate, we will let you see the personal information we hold about you and correct it if it is wrong. If we do not allow you access to any part of the personal information we hold about you, we will tell you why. If you wish to obtain access to your personal information held by us, or to request us to correct any errors in that information, please contact us by:

  * phoning the Form-Assistance.com Customer Support Team on 1-877-249-3543 
  * emailing us at [support@Form-Assistance.com](mailto:support@Form-Assistance.com)

If you wish to be removed from our customer's mailing list, please send us an email at: [support@Form-Assistance.com](mailto:support@Form-Assistance.com) or you may enter the registered email address and click Remove from Mail

**Who should you contact if you have concerns about our handling of personal information?**

If you have any queries or concerns about the manner in which we have handled your personal information, please write to the email address mentioned above. We will send you written acknowledgement of your correspondence. We will investigate your query or concern and will advise you of the steps we have taken to answer or resolve it.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time at our discretion and without notice. At any time, the latest version is available from our website at Form-Assistance.com issued on October 10, 2011.

**Our Internet Privacy Policy**

**Internet Privacy Commitment**

This document describes the policy of Form-Assistance.com regarding information received about you during visits to our web sites. The amount and type of information received depends on how you use our sites. This website does not contain links to other sites operated by third parties. This privacy statement is for this web site only. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each website that collects your personally identifiable information.

**Collection of personally identifiable information**

There are instances where Form-Assistance.com requests personally identifiable information to provide the web site visitor with a service or correspondence (for example, promotions). These information, such as name, mailing address, email address, type of request and possibly additional information, are collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data by Form-Assistance.com and are used to fulfill your request. If you tell us that the information should not be used as a basis for further contact, we will respect your request. The information you provide is used by Form-Assistance.com to improve the services we provide you. It is never provided to any other company for that company's independent use. Information which Form-Assistance.com holds about you may be transferred overseas to the secure facilities of Form-Assistance.com. If your information is transferred overseas it will remain subject to strict security safeguards. For further information regarding the handling of Form-Assistance.com of your personal information or to request a copy of the privacy policy of Form-Assistance.com or information we hold about you, you may email us at [support@Form-Assistance.com](mailto:support@Form-Assistance.com)

**Use of "Cookies"**

We do not use cookies on our website. 

**Internet Services**

To use the Internet Services of Form-Assistance.com, we may require a certain amount of personally identifying information (examples are: name, credit card number, vehicle identification number, address, business name, etc.) that we can use to verify you as a Form-Assistance.com Customer (or to meet your request). We use this information to identify and access data in the existing relationship we have with you to provide you with the requested services. We request electronic mail addresses (email) as an alternate means of contacting you.

**Electronic mail sent to us that contains personal information**

Internet users may decide to send Form-Assistance.com personally identifying information, for example, in a message containing information about your Form-Assistance.com product or service. Form-Assistance.com will only use this information to identify the user as a Form-Assistance.com customer and to determine how to respond to the electronic mail. We will not use this information other than to resolve the matter identified in the email. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. A revised Privacy Policy will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date. Any revisions will be posted at least 10 days prior to its effective date.
